A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, President, Detlev Bronk, Personal and Professional papers FA965
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Personal and professional papers
  - Bronk Japan Trip, NAS, NRC, National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis, 1947-1952
    - Bronk Correspondence-R, 1948-1949 (Box 36, Folder 50)
    - University of PA, Research Advisory Committee, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 51)
    - Review of Scientific Instruments, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 52)
    - Roe, Ann, 1946-1947 (Box 36, Folder 53)
    - Royal Society, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 54)
    - Bronk Correspondence-S, 1947-1951 (Box 36, Folder 55)
    - Sigma Xi, 1947-1948 (Box 36, Folder 56)
    - American Philosophical Society, 1949-1951 (Box 36, Folder 57)
    - Bronk Correspondence-A, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 58)
    - Academie des Sciences, Paris, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 59)
    - Air Force Association, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 60)
    - Air Materiel Command, 1948-1952 (Box 36, Folder 61)
    - American Academy of Arts and Science, 1949-1950 (Box 36, Folder 62)
    - American Neurological Society, 1950-1952 (Box 36, Folder 63)
    - American Philosophical Society, 1950-1952 (Box 36, Folder 64)
    - Armed Forces, NRC Vision Committee, 1948-1951 (Box 36, Folder 65)
    - Armed Forces, NRC Vision Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 36, Folder 66)
  - NRC, 1940-1948
    - National Research Council (NRC), Advisory Commission to the Council of National Defense, 1941 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - NRC, Air Sickness, 1941 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - NRC, Aviation Bulletin, 1943-1946 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Brazil Trip, 1945 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - NRC, Burchell, Howard, Post-War Aviation in Germany, 1945 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - NRC, Committee on Aviation Medicine, 1941-1943 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - NRC, Coordination of Air Surgeon's Office, 1943 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - NRC, Correspondence, 1935-1936 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - NRC, Correspondence, 1940 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - NRC, Correspondence, 1941 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - NRC, Correspondence, 1942 January-March (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - NRC, Correspondence, 1942 April-August (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - NRC, Correspondence, 1942 September-December (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - NRC, Correspondence, 1943 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - NRC, Correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - NRC, Correspondence, 1946 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - NRC, Correspondence, 1947 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - NRC, Correspondence, 1948 January-August (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - NRC, Correspondence, 1948 August (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - NRC, Correspondence, 1948 September-December (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - NRC, Dark Adaption, 1941 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - NRC, Dark Adaption, 1941-1943 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - NRC, International Relations, 1945 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Johnson Foundation War Contracts, 1940-1943 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - NRC, Report by Carlson, Brink and Bronk on Oxygen Consumption, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - NRC, Oxygen Saturation, 1941 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - NRC, Plans and Outlines for Manuscripts, 1945 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - NRC, Post-War Legislation for Scientific Research, 1945 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - NRC, Post-War Legislation for Scientific Research, 1945-1946 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - NRC, Post-War Legislation for Scientific Research, 1945-1946 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - NRC, Pressure Chamber Studies, 1941 (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - NRC, Tarnish, 1941 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - OSRD, 1943-1947
    - Office of Scientific Research and Development (OSRD), Committee of Medical Research (CMR), 1943 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - OSRD, Applied Mathematics Panel, 1944-1946 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - OSRD, Applied Phsychology Panel, 1943-1946 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - OSRD, CMR, Forms, 1943-1946 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - OSRD, CMR, Deliveries, 1943-1946 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - OSRD, CMR, National Defense Research Committee Liaison, 1943-1944 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - OSRD, CMR, 1944 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - OSRD, CMR, 1945 January-June (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - OSRD, CMR, 1945 July-December (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - OSRD, CMR, 1946 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - OSRD, Conscientious Objectors, Aviation Medicine, 1943-1944 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - OSRD, Division of Aviation Medicine, 1944-1945 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - OSRD, CMR, Contracts, 1944-1945 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - OSRD, CMR, 1944-1946 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - OSRD-D., CMR, 1944-1945 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - OSRD, Divisions and Organization of CMR, 1943-1946 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - OSRD, Division Meetings, CMR, 1944-1945 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - OSRD, Envelope Inventory Record, 1945-1947 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - OSRD-F., CMR, 1944-1946 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - OSRD-H., CMR, 1945-1946 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - OSRD, Haynes, Constance, 1945 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - OSRD, History of Science in the United States (Shryock), 1946 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - OSRD, Keefer, Chester S., 1945-1947 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - OSRD-L, CMR, 1945 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - OSRD-M, CMR, 1944-1945 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - OSRD, Manuscript List, 1945 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - OSRD, Mayne, Robert, 1945 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - OSRD, Montgomery, F.R. Mrs., CMR, 1945-1946 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - OSRD-N, CMR, 1946 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - OSRD, Bush, Vannevar, 1942-1946 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - OSRD, Richards, A.N., CMR, 1944-1946 (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - OSRD, CMR History, 1946-1947 (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - OSRD, History, 1945-1946 (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - OSRD, Palmer Committee, 1943 (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - OSRD, Committee on Publications of OSRD, 1944 (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - OSRD, Quarterly Reports, Aviation Medicine, 1944-1945 (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - OSRD, Records Section, (Turner), 1944-1946 (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - OSRD-S, CMR, 1945-1946 (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - OSRD, Scientific Personnel Office (Bailey), 1944-1945 (Box 38, Folder 39)
    - OSRD, Committee on Sensory Devices, 1944 (Box 38, Folder 40)
    - OSRD, Stewart, Irving, Contract Termination Blanks, 1945 (Box 38, Folder 41)
    - OSRD-T, CMR, 1945-1946 (Box 38, Folder 42)
    - OSRD, Telephone Charges, 1945-1946 (Box 38, Folder 43)
    - OSRD, Section 12.1, National Defense Research Committee (NDRC), 1943 (Box 38, Folder 44)
    - OSRD, Section 16.1, NDRC, (Dunham), 1943-1946 (Box 38, Folder 45)
    - OSRD, Section 16.5, NDRC, (Forsythe), 1944-1946 (Box 38, Folder 46)
    - OSRD, Section 17.1, NDRC, 1943-1944 (Box 38, Folder 47)
    - OSRD, AAF Materiel Command, 1944-1945 (Box 38, Folder 48)
    - OSRD, Bills of Lading, 1946 (Box 38, Folder 49)
    - OSRD, Certificates of Merit, 1945 (Box 38, Folder 50)
    - OSRD, Classified Material, 1945-1946 (Box 38, Folder 51)
    - OSRD, Communication (Addresses), 1946 (Box 38, Folder 52)
    - OSRD, Communications, Telephone Procedure, 1944-1945 (Box 38, Folder 53)
    - OSRD, Declassification Lists, 1946 (Box 38, Folder 54)
    - OSRD, Demobilization, 1944-1946 (Box 38, Folder 55)
    - OSRD, Draft, 1943-1945 (Box 38, Folder 56)
    - OSRD, Fiscal, 1943-1945 (Box 38, Folder 57)
    - OSRD, Franked Envelopes, 1945 (Box 38, Folder 58)
    - OSRD, Information for Contracts, 1941-1945 (Box 38, Folder 59)
    - OSRD, Navy Procedure, 1945 (Box 38, Folder 60)
    - OSRD, Obsolete Material, 1945-1946 (Box 38, Folder 61)
    - OSRD, Organization, 1945-1946 (Box 38, Folder 62)
    - OSRD, Personnel Clearance, 1942-1945 (Box 38, Folder 63)
    - OSRD, Personnel, Employment and Release, 1942-1945 (Box 38, Folder 64)
    - OSRD, Personnel, 1945 (Box 38, Folder 65)
    - OSRD, Personnel, 1945 (Box 38, Folder 66)
    - OSRD, Property and Contract Transfer, 1944-1945 (Box 38, Folder 67)
    - OSRD, 1944-1946 (Box 38, Folder 68)
    - OSRD, 1942-1947 (Box 38, Folder 69)
    - OSRD, Inventions and Patents, 1943-1945 (Box 38, Folder 70)
    - OSRD, Reproduction and Distribution Reports, 1944-1946 (Box 38, Folder 71)
  - Institutions, Foundations, Commission for Financing Higher Education, 1948-1950
    - List of U.S. Institutions, undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Commission for Financing Higher Education, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Commission for Financing Higher Education, 1950 January-September (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Commission for Financing Higher Education, 1950 November (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Commission for Financing Higher Education, 1950 November-December (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Commission for Financing Higher Education, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Commission for Financing Higher Education, 1948 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Commission on the Organization of the Executive Branch of the Government, 1948 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Commission on the Organization of the Executive Branch of the Government, 1949-1950 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Cosmos Club, 1949-1953 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Armed Forces Medical Policy Council, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Population Upsurge in the United States, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Bronk Correspondence-D, 1949-1953 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Department of the Army, 1952-1953 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Bronk Correspondence-E, 1949-1951 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Bronk Correspondence-F, Federal Security Agency, 1949-1953 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Forest Genetics Research Foundation, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Foreign Service Educational Foundation, 1951 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Office of Military Goverment for Germany, National Research Council, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Federation of American Scientists, 1949-1952 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Ford Foundation, 1949-1953 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Fourteen West Hamilton Street Club, 1949-1950 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Bronk Correspondence-G, 1948-1951 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Geophysical Research Directorate, 1949-1950 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Bronk Correspondence-H, 1949-1953 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Hall of Fame, 1950-1952 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Bronk Correspondence-I, 1948-1950 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Institute for Cancer Research, 1950-1953 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Institute for Cancer Research, 1949-1950 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Institute for Cancer Research, 1948-1950 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF), 1950-1975
    - National Science Foundation (NSF), Loose Papers, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - NSF, Bronk's Appointment to NAS Board Ad Hoc Committee, 1964-1975 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - NSF, Loose Papers, 1973-1974 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - NSF, Ad hoc Committee on 25th Anniversary, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - NSF, U.S. Congress, House Bill to Establish Congressional Office of Science and Technology, 1958-1963 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - NSF, 1951-1968 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - NSF, History, 1953-1969 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - NSF, Committee on Public Understanding of Science, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - NSF, Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - NSF, 1968-1970 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - NSF, Meeting, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - NSF, Science Service Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - NSF, Foundations, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - NSF, Vernice Anderson's Gift, 1967-1968 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - NSF, Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - NSF, Correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - NSF, Barnard, C.I., 1956 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - NSF, "Anton Brunn", USS, 1962-1963 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - NSF, Calnek, Dr. Edward, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - NSF, American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1960-1963 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - NSF, Meeting, 1951 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - NSF, Bronk Appointment Letter from President Harry Truman, 1950 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - NSF, National Science Board, 1956-1963 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - NSF, Budget, 1955-1965 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - NSF, Grants, 1956-1964 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - NSF, 1959-1965 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - NSF, Moe Commission, 1963-1964 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - NSF, Antarctic, 1957-1967 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - NSF, Policy Data, 1954-1960 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - NSF, Bronk Election to Chairman; of NSF, 1955-1964 (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - NSF, Bronk Retirement Dinner, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - NSF, IGY Satellite, 1956-1959 (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - NSF, Congressional Hearing Reports, 1958-1963 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1939-1970
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS), 1939-1951 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - AAAS, 1951 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - AAAS, 1952 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - AAAS, 1952 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - AAAS, 1953-1954 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - AAAS, Retiring Presidential Address, 1954-1955 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Meyerhoff Affair, 1953 March (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Meyerhoff Affair, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Meyerhoff Affair, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Meyerhoff Affair, 1953 April (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - AAAS, 1971-1975 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - AAAS, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - AAAS, Phi Beta Kappa Lecture, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - AAAS, Science Service Committee on Development, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - AAAS, Symposium, State Science Policy, December 30, 1969, 1969-1970 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - AAAS, Science and Scientific Monthly, 1953-1967 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - AAAS, United Chapters of Phi Beta Kappa, 1955 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - AAAS, Science Service, 1965-1967 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - AAAS, 1958-1966 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - AAAS, 1952-1957 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - AAAS, By Laws, Meeting, 1955-1956 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - AAAS, 134th Annual Meeting, NYC, 1967 December 26-31 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - AAAS, 134th Annual Meeting, NYC, 1967 December 26-31 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - AAAS, 1967-1968 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - AAAS, 134th Annual Meeting, NYC, 1967 December 26-31 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - AAAS, 1967 Meeting, Polanyi Symposium (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - AAAS, 1967 Meeting, Science Writers (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - AAAS, 1967 Meeting, Rockefeller Tours (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - AAAS, 1967 Meeting, Faraday Exhibit and Lectures (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - AAAS, 1967 Meeting, Science and Secrecy Symposium (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - AAAS, 1967 Meeting, Press (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - AAAS, 1967 Meeting, AAAS Bulletin (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - AAAS, 1967 Meeting, Visits to NYC Scientific Institutions (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - AAAS, 1967 Meeting, Romer's Dinner (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - AAAS, 1967 Meeting, Bronk Reception (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - AAAS, 1967 Meeting, Television Coverage (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - AAAS, 1967 Meeting, John Scott Medal (Box 41, Folder 37)
    - AAAS, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO), 1950-1953
    - United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization, (UNESCO), 1, 1950 January (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - UNESCO, 1950 April-May (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - UNESCO, 1950 June (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - UNESCO, 1950 June (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - UNESCO, 1950 June (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - UNESCO, 1950 July (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - UNESCO, 1950 July (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - UNESCO, 1950 August-October (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - UNESCO, 1950 October-November (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - UNESCO, 1951 January-March (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - UNESCO, 1951 March (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - UNESCO, 1951 April-May (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - UNESCO, 1951 May (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - UNESCO, 1951 June-October (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - UNESCO, 1952 February-November (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - UNESCO, 1952 December-1953 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute (RPI), 1964-1975
    - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute (RPI), Alumni Convocation, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - RPI, Alumni Convocation, 1972-1973 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - RPI, Alumni Convocation, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - RPI, 150th Anniversary Program, 1965-1969 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - RPI, Commencement, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - RPI, Hartford Graduate Center, 1966-1967 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - RPI, Union Dedication, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - RPI, Ad hoc Committee for President Folsom, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - RPI, Ad hoc Committee on Operation and Composition of the Board, 1968-1969 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - RPI, Committees, undated (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - RPI, Development Committee, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - RPI, Finance Committee, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - RPI, Goals for Rensselaer Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - RPI, Honorary Degree Committee, 1965-1967 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - RPI, Investment Committee, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - RPI, Presidential Selection Committee, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - RPI, Presidential Selection Committee, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - RPI, Presidential Selection Committee, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - RPI, Presidential Selection Committee, The Polytechnic, 1971-1975 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - RPI, Presidential Committee, 1965-1967 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - RPI, Trustees Academic Affairs Committee, 1965-1967 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - RPI, Visiting and Advisory Committee, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - RPI, Chairman of the Board of Trustees, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - RPI, Chairman of the Board of Trustees, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - RPI, Chairman of the Board of Trustees, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - RPI, Selection of the New Chairman of the Board, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - RPI, Trustee File, 1964-1966 (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - RPI, Trustee File, 1970 January-April (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - RPI, Trustee File, 1970 June-December (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - RPI, Trustee File, 1975-1976 (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - RPI, Trustee Topics, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - New York State Science and Technology Foundation (NYSSTF), 1964-1975
    - New York State Science and Technology Foundation (NYSSTF), Appointments, 1964-1972 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - NYSSTF, Budget Hearing, 1967-1968 May (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - NYSSTF, Budget Hearing, 1968 June-December (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - NYSSTF, Correspondence, 1961-1964 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - NYSSTF, Correspondence, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - NYSSTF, Correspondence, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - NYSSTF, Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - NYSSTF, Correspondence, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - NYSSTF, Correspondence, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - NYSSTF, Correspondence, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - NYSSTF, Correspondence, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - NYSSTF, Correspondence, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - NYSSTF, Correspondence, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - NYSSTF, Correspondence, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - NYSSTF, Correspondence, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - NYSSTF, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - NYSSTF, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Organizational Affiliations A - W, 1943-1945
    - Bronk Correspondence-A, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - American Institute of Physics, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - American Neurological Association, 1944 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - American Philosophical Society, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Aviation Physiologists Bulletin, 1943-1945 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Air Surgeon's Office, circa 1944 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - American Physiological Society, Symposium on Biophysics, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - American Physical Society, Bulletins, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Antivivisection Bill, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Aviation Physiologists Bulletin, Bibliography, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Aviation Physiologists Training Program, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Applicants for Position, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Adrians, Jennet P. and Richard, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - American Physiological Society, Biophysics Section, 1944 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Bronk Correspondence-B, 1943-1945 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Bethesda, Maryland Naval Medical Research Institute, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Biological Abstracts, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Biology Visiting Committee (MIT), 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Boats, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Books for Devastated Libraries, Conference, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Bronk Correspondence-C, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Calendars, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - Committee on Aviation Medicine, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Camps, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - Century Association, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - Chance, Britton, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - Clippings, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 27)
    - Columbia Army Air Base, 1944 (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - Cosmos Club, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - Council on Development (University of PA), 1944 (Box 45, Folder 30)
    - Bronk Correspondence-D, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 31)
    - Dean's Office, Medical School, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 32)
    - Draft Correspondence, 1943 (Box 45, Folder 33)
    - Dutcher, R. Adams, 1944 (Box 45, Folder 34)
    - Bronk Correspondence-E, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 35)
    - English-North American Trip, (Diary Aug 22-28), circa 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 36)
    - Bronk Correspondence-F, 1943-1945 (Box 45, Folder 37)
    - Fulton, John, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 38)
    - Fatigue, circa 1944 (Box 45, Folder 39)
    - Finance, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 40)
    - Flexner, Louis B, National Research Council, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 41)
    - Bronk Correspondence-G, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 42)
    - Grant Committee (American Philosophical Society), 1943-1944 (Box 45, Folder 43)
    - Graduate Schools, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 44)
    - Bronk Correspondence-H, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 45)
    - Halloran General Hospital, 1944 (Box 45, Folder 46)
    - Handbook of Respiratory Data in Aviation, NRC, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 47)
    - Hafkenschiel, Joseph H., 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 48)
    - Hutchinson, W.G., 1944 (Box 45, Folder 49)
    - Bronk Correspondence-I, 1944 (Box 45, Folder 50)
    - Institute of Biology, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 51)
    - Insurance, Personnel and Equipment at Johnson Foundation, 1943-1944 (Box 45, Folder 52)
    - Irving, Laurence, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 53)
    - Bronk Correspondence-J, 1944 (Box 45, Folder 54)
    - Johnson Foundation, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 55)
    - Journal of Cellular and Comparative Physiology, 1943-1944 (Box 45, Folder 56)
    - Journal of Industrial Biology, (Dr. Gray), 1945 (Box 45, Folder 57)
    - Bronk Correspondence-K, 1943-1945 (Box 45, Folder 58)
    - Bronk Correspondence-L, 1943-1945 (Box 45, Folder 59)
    - Lawrenceville, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 60)
    - Bronk Correspondence-M, 1943-1945 (Box 45, Folder 61)
    - Macmullan, Louise, 1944 (Box 45, Folder 62)
    - MacKay, Eaton, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 63)
    - Marine Biological Laboratory, Woods Hole, MA, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 64)
    - Monthly Science News, 1943 (Box 45, Folder 65)
    - Mudd, Stuart, 1943 (Box 45, Folder 66)
    - Bronk Correspondence-N, 1943-1944 (Box 45, Folder 67)
    - National Research Council, 1943-1944 (Box 45, Folder 68)
    - Navy, 1943-1944 (Box 45, Folder 69)
    - Neurology, 1943-1944 (Box 45, Folder 70)
    - New York Philharmonic Symphony, "Science Looks Forward", Broadcast Material, January 28 (Box 45, Folder 71)
    - Newsletter - Navy Department, 1943-1944 (Box 45, Folder 72)
    - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, Scottish Rite Fund, circa 1943-1944 (Box 45, Folder 73)
    - Bronk Correspondence-O, 1943-1944 (Box 45, Folder 74)
    - Optical Society of America, 1944 (Box 45, Folder 75)
    - Oxygen and Anoxia Subcommittee, 1943-1944 (Box 45, Folder 76)
    - Bronk Correspondence-P, 1943-1944 (Box 45, Folder 77)
    - Pepper, Perry, 1944 (Box 45, Folder 78)
    - Philadelphia Tri-State District, circa 1944 (Box 45, Folder 79)
    - Bronk Correspondence-R, 1943-1944 (Box 45, Folder 80)
    - Dr. Richard's Office, 1943-1944 (Box 45, Folder 81)
    - Review of Scientific Instruments, 1943 (Box 45, Folder 82)
    - Bronk Correspondence-S, 1943-1944 (Box 45, Folder 83)